(Sheldon:)I'm sorry, I bet my sweet what?
(Sheldon:)Well, all right. We're on our way.
(Leonard:)What's going on?
Well, it would seem Amy is drunk
in a liquor-store parking lot.
(Leonard:)Really? Amy?
(Sheldon:)Leonard, be glad you can't keep a woman.
They are a handful.
(Amy:)Oh, look. It's Sheldon and little Leonard.
Hi, Iittle Leonard.
- Hi, Amy.
- Hey, Cuddles.
(Leonard:)Cuddles?
(Sheldon:)Yes, Cuddles. We cuddled.
Grow up, Leonard.
(Leonard:)Amy, what are you doing here?
(Amy:)Well, I came here
to get a bottle of wine...
(Amy:)...like Penny taught me to do
when you're sad.
(Leonard:)Yeah, but why didn't you go back
to your apartment?
Didn't you go to high school?
Parking lots are where cool kids hang out.
(Amy:)Not that the rat bastards
ever invited me.